{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which is the most popular JavaScript framework?",
      "options": ["Angular", "React", "Svelte", "Vue"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which company invented React?",
      "options": ["Google", "Apple", "Netflix", "Facebook"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the fundamental building block of React apps?",
      "options": ["Components", "Blocks", "Elements", "Effects"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What's the name of the syntax we use to describe the UI in React components?",
      "options": ["FBJ", "Babel", "JSX", "ES2015"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How does data flow naturally in React apps?",
      "options": [
        "From parents to children",
        "From children to parents",
        "Both ways",
        "The developers decides"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "How to pass data into a child component?",
      "options": ["State", "Props", "PropTypes", "Parameters"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "When to use derived state?",
      "options": [
        "Whenever the state should not trigger a re-render",
        "Whenever the state can be synchronized with an effect",
        "Whenever the state should be accessible to all components",
        "Whenever the state can be computed from another state variable"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "What triggers a UI re-render in React?",
      "options": [
        "Running an effect",
        "Passing props",
        "Updating state",
        "Adding event listeners to DOM elements"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "When do we directly \"touch\" the DOM in React?",
      "options": [
        "When we need to listen to an event",
        "When we need to change the UI",
        "When we need to add styles",
        "Almost never"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "In what situation do we use a callback to update state?",
      "options": [
        "When updating the state will be slow",
        "When the updated state is very data-intensive",
        "When the state update should happen faster",
        "When the new state depends on the previous state"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "If we pass a function to useState, when will that function be called?",
      "options": [
        "On each re-render",
        "Each time we update the state",
        "Only on the initial render",
        "The first time we update the state"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which hook to use for an API request on the component's initial render?",
      "options": ["useState", "useEffect", "useRef", "useReducer"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which variables should go into the useEffect dependency array?",
      "options": [
        "Usually none",
        "All our state variables",
        "All state and props referenced in the effect",
        "All variables needed for clean up"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "An effect will always run on the initial render.",
      "options": [
        "True",
        "It depends on the dependency array",
        "False",
        "In depends on the code in the effect"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "When will an effect run if it doesn't have a dependency array?",
      "options": [
        "Only when the component mounts",
        "Only when the component unmounts",
        "The first time the component re-renders",
        "Each time the component is re-rendered"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    }
  ],
  "cities": [
    {
      "cityName": "Lisbon",
      "country": "Portugal",
      "emoji": "ðŸ‡µðŸ‡¹",
      "date": "2027-10-31T15:59:59.138Z",
      "notes": "My favorite city so far!",
      "position": {
        "lat": 38.727881642324164,
        "lng": -9.140900099907554
      },
      "id": 73930385
    },
    {
      "cityName": "Madrid",
      "country": "Spain",
      "emoji": "ðŸ‡ªðŸ‡¸",
      "date": "2027-07-15T08:22:53.976Z",
      "notes": "",
      "position": {
        "lat": 40.46635901755316,
        "lng": -3.7133789062500004
      },
      "id": 17806751
    },
    {
      "cityName": "Berlin",
      "country": "Germany",
      "emoji": "ðŸ‡©ðŸ‡ª",
      "date": "2027-02-12T09:24:11.863Z",
      "notes": "Amazing ðŸ˜ƒ",
      "position": {
        "lat": 52.53586782505711,
        "lng": 13.376933665713324
      },
      "id": 98443197
    },
    {
      "cityName": "Nijar",
      "country": "Spain",
      "emoji": "ðŸ‡ªðŸ‡¸",
      "date": "2023-04-03T07:47:59.202Z",
      "notes": "",
      "position": {
        "lat": "36.967508314568164",
        "lng": "-2.13128394200588"
      },
      "id": 98443198
    }
  ]
}
